{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450917572","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450917572"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450924180","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450924179"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450930804","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450930804"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450938261","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450938261"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450947271","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450947271"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450953469","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450953469"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450960913","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450960912"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450969920","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450969919"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450976544","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450976544"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450983986","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450983986"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450990594","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450990594"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450997219","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450997219"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549450997984","data":{"timestamp":" 1549450997983"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" cb16ba3c-8153-43d8-9c0b-b1f53f33c817"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" o1_3_9_2"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451023483","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451023483"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451030940","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451030940"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451039948","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451039948"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_9_7"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451046614","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451046614"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_8_5"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451053269","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451053269"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451060745","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451060745"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451069803","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451069803"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_7_4_8"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451076004","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451076004"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451083444","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451083444"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451092455","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451092454"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_4_2_6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451098651","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451098651"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_5_8_6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451105277","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451105277"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:0..9.by.1.des","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1549451112752","data":{"timestamp":" 1549451112752"," userId":" 6115001261"," sessionId":" 6115001261_20190206_140138"," gameId":" ff3c9e49-b025-4b38-bb42-d8a5c8c3e6da"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_0..9.by.1.des"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_6_4_7"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}